Register of the Polish Subject Collection, 1918-2014
Hoover Institution Archives
- Władysław Chojnacki collection, 1944-1953
  - Anti-Soviet and Anti-Communist underground materials, 1944-1953
    - Periodicals - Wiesci, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 63: 15)
    - Periodicals - W Ogniu Walki, 1944 (Box-folder 63: 16)
    - Periodicals - Wola Narodu, 1944 (Box-folder 63: 17)
    - Periodicals - Wolna Polska, 1946 (Box-folder 63: 18)
    - Periodicals - Wolne Slowo, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 19)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc, 1946 (Box-folder 63: 20)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc, 1951 (Box-folder 63: 21)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc I Demokracja, 1944 (Box-folder 63: 22)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc I Niepodleglosc, 1946 (Box-folder 63: 23)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc I Niezawislosc, 1946 (Box-folder 63: 24)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc I Prawda, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 25)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosci Zew, 1946 (Box-folder 63: 26)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc Slowa, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 63: 27)
    - Periodicals - Wschod, 1945 (Box-folder 63: 28)
    - Periodicals - W Sluzbie Ojczyzny, 1946 (Box-folder 63: 29)
    - Periodicals - W Swietle Prawdy, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 63: 30)
    - Periodicals - Wydawnictwo Polski Niezawislej, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 1)
    - Periodicals - Wytrwamy, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 64: 2)
    - Periodicals - Wytrwamy, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 64: 3)
    - Periodicals - Wyzwolenie, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 4)
    - Periodicals - Zamojska Agencja Informacyjna, 1944 (Box-folder 64: 5)
    - Periodicals - Zarzewie, 1950 (Box-folder 64: 6)
    - Periodicals - Z Chwili, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 7)
    - Periodicals - Zerwijmy Peta, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 8)
    - Periodicals - Ze Swiata, 1944 (Box-folder 64: 9)
    - Periodicals - Zew, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 10)
    - Periodicals - Zew Podziemi, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 11)
    - Periodicals - Znaleziono Przy Mnie, 1946 (Box-folder 64: 12)
    - Periodicals - Z Nami Wszyscy, 1946 (Box-folder 64: 13)
    - Periodicals - Znicz, 1946 (Box-folder 64: 14)
    - Periodicals - Z Podziemi, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 15)
    - Periodicals - Z Polski I Swiata, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 16)
    - Periodicals - Zwyciestwo, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 17)
    - Periodicals - Zolnierz Obywatel, 1944 (Box-folder 64: 18)
    - Periodicals - Zywia I Bronia, 1945 (Box-folder 64: 19)
    - Foreign Publications about Poland, 1944 (Box-folder 64: 20)
    - Przewodnik Terenowy - zbior inz. L. Kummanta, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 64: 21)
      Periodicals: Honor I Ojczyzna, Glos, Informator, Echa Lesne, Do Potegi Polski, Sojusznik, Ku Wolnosci, Narod w Walce, Mysl Niezalezna, Nasz Biuletyn, Reduta, Niepodleglosc, Polskie Slowo, Wiesci, Orzel Bialy, Wolnosc I Niezawislosc, Wytrwamy, Mloda Polska, Zolnierz Wielkiej Polski
    - Przewodnik Terenowy - zbior inz. L. Kummanta, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 64: 22)
      Booklets and Posters
    - Przewodnik Terenowy - zbior inz. L. Kummanta, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 64: 23)
      Periodicals: Serwis Informacyjno-Propagandowy, Slowo Polskie, Sojusznik, Walka, Informacja Chrzescijanska, Zrab
    - Periodicals - Index (Box-folder 88: 1)
    - Periodicals - ABC Mlodych, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 2)
    - Periodicals - AK Gazetka Scienna, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 3)
    - Periodicals - Agencja Prasowa, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 4)
    - Periodicals - Agencja Socjalistyczna, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 5)
    - Periodicals - Agencja Spoleczno-Polityczna, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 6)
    - Periodicals - Alarm, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 7)
    - Periodicals - Baszta, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 8)
    - Periodicals - Biel I Czerwien, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 9)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 10)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn "C", 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 11)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Harcerskiego Ruchu Antykomunistycznego, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 12)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 13)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 14)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 15)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny dla Duchowienstwa, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 16)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Informacyjny Ziemi Bialostockiej, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 17)
    - Periodicals - Biuletyn Wewnetrzny, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 18)
    - Periodicals - CBW, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 19)
    - Periodicals - Czas Wyzwolenia, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 20)
    - Periodicals - Czyn, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 21)
    - Periodicals - Dawnym Szlakiem, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 22)
    - Periodicals - Dokumenty Programowe AK, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 23)
    - Periodicals - Echa Lesne, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 24)
    - Periodicals - Gazeta Malopolska, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 25)
    - Periodicals - Glos Jednosci Polskiej, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 26)
    - Periodicals - Glos Opozycji, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 27)
    - Periodicals - Glos Podziemia, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 28)
    - Periodicals - Glos Prawdy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 29)
    - Periodicals - Glos spod Ziemi, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 30)
    - Periodicals - Glos Ziemi Bialostockiej, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 31)
    - Periodicals - Glos z nad Narwi, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 32)
    - Periodicals - Grupa Dywersyjna AK "Blyskawica", 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 33)
    - Periodicals - Informacje Polskie, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 34)
    - Periodicals - Informator, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 35)
    - Periodicals - Informator, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 36)
    - Periodicals - Jestem Polakiem, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 88: 37)
    - Periodicals - Komunikat Informacyjny, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 1)
    - Periodicals - Konspekt Propagandowy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 2)
    - Periodicals - Ku Wolnosci, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 3)
    - Periodicals - Ku Zwyciestwu, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 4)
    - Periodicals - List z Lasu, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 5)
    - Periodicals - Lubelska Agencja Informacyjna, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 6)
    - Periodicals - Lubelski Biuletyn Radiowy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 7)
    - Periodicals - Materialy dla Terenu, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 8)
    - Periodicals - Monitor Bialostocki, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 9)
    - Periodicals - Mysl Niezalezna, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 10)
    - Periodicals - Na Strazy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 11)
    - Periodicals - Narodowy Ruch Antybolszewicki, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 12)
    - Periodicals - Narod w Walce, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 13)
    - Periodicals - Narod w Walce, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 14)
    - Periodicals - Nasluch Radiowy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 15)
    - Periodicals - Nasz Biuletyn, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 16)
    - Periodicals - Niepodleglosc, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 17)
    - Periodicals - Niezawislosc, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 18)
    - Periodicals - Nowy Zew, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 19)
    - Periodicals - Odwet, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 20)
    - Periodicals - Ojczyzna Krucjata, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 21)
    - Periodicals - Orleta, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 22)
    - Periodicals - Orzel Bialy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 23)
    - Periodicals - Patria, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 24)
    - Periodicals - P.I.R., 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 25)
    - Periodicals - Plomien, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 26)
    - Periodicals - Pochodnia Zwyciestwa, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 27)
    - Periodicals - Pogadanka Zolnierska, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 28)
    - Periodicals - Polonia, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 29)
    - Periodicals - Polska Informacja Polityczna, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 30)
    - Periodicals - Polska I Swiat, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 31)
    - Periodicals - Polska Niezawisla, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 32)
    - Periodicals - Polska Niezawisla, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 33)
    - Periodicals - Polska Walczaca, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 89: 34)
    - Periodicals - Polskie Slowo, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 1)
    - Periodicals - Prawda, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 2)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Krajowy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 3)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Krajowy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 4)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Polityczny, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 5)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Prasowy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 6)
    - Periodicals - Przeglad Zagraniczny, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 7)
    - Periodicals - Puszcza Szumi, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 8)
    - Periodicals - Reduta, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 9)
    - Periodicals - Samoobrona, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 10)
    - Periodicals - Serwis Informacyjny Inki, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 11)
    - Periodicals - Serwis Informacyjny Inki dla Prasy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 12)
    - Periodicals - Serwis Informacyjny Inki dla Wladz, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 13)
    - Periodicals - Serwis Specjalny Inki, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 14)
    - Periodicals - Slowo Polskie, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 15)
    - Periodicals - Slowo Polskie, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 16)
    - Periodicals - Slowo Polskie, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 17)
    - Periodicals - Sowizdrzal, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 18)
    - Periodicals - Straznica Podziemi, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 19)
    - Periodicals - Straznica Sumienia, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 20)
    - Periodicals - Sygnal, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 21)
    - Periodicals - Szydlo, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 22)
    - Periodicals - Teka, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 90: 23)
    - Periodicals - Uwagi Na Czasie, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 1)
    - Periodicals - W Swietle Prawdy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 2)
    - Periodicals - Walka, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 3)
    - Periodicals - Walka, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 4)
    - Periodicals - Walka o Przewage Ducha, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 5)
    - Periodicals - Warszawski Glos Narodowy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 6)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 7)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Biezace, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 8)
    - Periodicals - Wiadomosci Radiowe, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 9)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 10)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 11)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc I Demokracja, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 12)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc I Niezawislosc, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 13)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc Slowa, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 14)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc Slowa, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 15)
    - Periodicals - Wolnosc Slowa, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 16)
    - Periodicals - WP Lwow, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 17)
    - Periodicals - Wschod, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 18)
    - Periodicals - Wszechpolak, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 19)
    - Periodicals - Wytrwamy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 20)
    - Periodicals - Z Nami Wszyscy, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 21)
    - Periodicals - Z Podziemi, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 22)
    - Periodicals - Zolnierz Obywatel, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 23)
    - Periodicals - Zolnierz Wielkiej Polski, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 91: 24)
    - Armia Krajowa (Home Army) - Publications, 1944 (Box-folder 92: 12)
    - Armia Krajowa (Home Army) - Flyers, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 92: 13--14)
    - Narodowe Sily Zbrojne (National Armed Forces) - Publications, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 92: 15--16)
    - Miscellaneous - Edward Brydak "Wspomnienia", Undated (Box-folder 94: 12)
    - Miscellaneous - Ludwika Kownacka "Ryciny", Undated (Box-folder 94: 13)
  - Publications of the Warsaw Uprising, 1944
    These materials are the publications of the Warsaw Uprising of August to September, 1944.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 1)
      "Armia Ludowa", No. 10, 22, 23, 25-31, 34, 35
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 2)
      "Barykada", pismo III rejonu A.K. daily issue No.1-25, evening issue 11-14, 16-20; suplement: Informacja Radiowa: No.1, 3-6, 10-11.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 3)
      "Barykada Powisla" No. 4-23, 25-26
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 4)
      "Barykada. Warszawa Walczy" No. 26-32, 34, 36-42, 44-46, 48-49, 51.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 5)
      "Barykada Wolnosci" Organ Robotniczej Partii Polskich Socjalistow. No. 142-145, 150, 152, 154-155.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 6)
      Biuletyn No.7
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 7)
      Biuletyn Centralnego Komitetu Ludowego, No. 2-8, 11-14, 16-20.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 8--9)
      Biuletyn Informacyjny. Wydanie Codzienne, No. 35/242 - 72/280, 74/283, 76/284, 78/286 - 81/289, 83/291-85/293, 87/295 - 97/305, 99/307-102/310; Dodatek Ilustrowany, No.1
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 10)
      13, 20, 31, 34, 72, 78, 79, 82, 87, 95.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 11)
      Biuletyn Okregu IV PPS Warszawa - Polnoc, No.13
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 12)
      Biuletyn Podokregu Nr. 2 Armii Ludowej, No. 46, 51, 53.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 13)
      "Brzask". Pismo Harcerskich Oddzialow Armii Krajowej, No. 11/38.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 14)
      "Czerniakow w Walce". Pismo Codzienne. No. 3, 5, 13, 14.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 15)
      "Komunikat radiofoniczny". No. 11, 12, 14, 31, 37, 144.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 16)
      "Biuletyn radiowy" No. 23
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 105: 17)
      Komunikat informacyjny
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 1)
      "Warszawski Glos Narodowy". No.25-30, 33, special issue
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 2)
      "Wielka Polska" No. 20-25, 31-32, 35, 12 sierpnia 1944
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 3)
      "Wiadomosci Powstancze", No.40-42.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 4)
      "Wiadomosci Radiowe", No. 24, 27, 28, 32, 34.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 5)
      "Wojsko Polskie", No. 1-3, 5-9.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 6)
      Wolna Polska, No. 115-116.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 7)
      "Z Pierwszej Linii Frontu", Aug. 10-26.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 8)
      "Zbrojne Wyzwolenie", No. 241.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 9)
      "Zryw", No. 37-39.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 10)
      "Zywia i Bronia", No. 10, 12-13, 15-18, 20-23.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 11)
      Flyers
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 106: 12--14)
      "Wiadomosci z Miasta i Wiadomosci Radiowe", No. 9-10, 13-16, 19, 23, 29-37, 39-40, 43, 46-52, 54, 56-59, 61-64, 71, 74, 76, 78, 80-83, 86-92, 94-96, 98-99, 101, 103-104, 107, 111.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 1)
      "Demokrata:codzienne pismo ilustrowane", No. 169/292, 171/294-185/308, 190/312-194/316, 205/327.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 2)
      "Dziennik Obwieszczen Rejonowego delegata Rzadu Warszawa-Poludnie". No. 1-7.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 3)
      "Dziennik Radiowy", No. 3, 37, 43-46, 49-59.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 4)
      "Dziennik Ustaw Rzeczypospolitej Polskiej. Czesc III", No. 1-2.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 5)
      "Dzien Warszawy. Popoludniowe Pismo Codzienne", No. 1005-1006, 1009, 1011-1013, 1016-1027, 1029, 1031, 1033, 1037, 1039, 1041.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 6)
      "Dzien Warszawy. Wydanie Poranne". No. 1028-1056, 1059-1060, 1061-1064.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 7)
      "Glos Starego Miasta", No. 6.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 9)
      Glos Warszawy, No. 65/158, 67/170
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 8)
      "Glos Demokracji", No. 1-3.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 10)
      Gazeta Polowa, No. 1.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 11)
      Komunikat Informacyjny, No. 17, 20.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 12)
      Komunikat Organizacyjny Polskiego Zwiazku Wolnosci, No. 11.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 13)
      Jednodniowka Katolicka
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 14)
      Glos Warszawy. Wydawnictwo Polskiej Partii Robotniczej, No. 167-168, 170, 173-178, 180-182.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 15)
      Iskra.Zwiazek Syndykalistow Polskich, No. 9-11, 59.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 16)
      Kobieta na Barykadzie, No. 1-4.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 17)
      Komunikat Informacyjny. Komenda Placu Odcinka Mokotow, No. 17, 22, 25-28, 30, 35, 37, 39, 41, 44, 46.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 18)
      Narod Walczy, No. 903
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 19)
      Na dzien 26 sierpnia. W swieto Matki Boskiej Czestochowskiej.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 20)
      Nowy Dzien, No. 905-908, 910-915.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 21)
      Nowy Swiat, No. 1-9, 11-12, 14-19.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 22)
      Polska Ilustrowana,No. 3.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 23)
      Polska Zwyciezy, No. 1-6.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 107: 24)
      Prawda. Pismo Polskich Katolikow Swieckich.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 1--3)
      Kurier Stoleczny, No. 1-22, 24, 30-31, 33-35, 36-39, 41-42, Kurier Stoleczny. Organ Stronnictwa Pracy. Wydanie Staromiejskie, No. 16-17.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 4)
      Rejonowka, No. 14-59
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 5--6)
      Robotnik. Centralny Organ P.P.S., No. 10-42, 44-70
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 7)
      Robotnik. Centralny Organ P.P.S. Lewica, No. 163, 167
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 8)
      Rzeczpospolita Polska, No. 16-46, 50-52, 60, 62-64, 66-78
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 9)
      Sprawa, No.106-107
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 10)
      Syndykalista, No. 1.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 11)
      Syndykalista. Syndykalistyczne Porozumienie Powstancze. No. 5, 7-8, 11-14, 16.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 12)
      Tydzien, No. 69-70.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 108: 13)
      Szaniec, No. 12, 14, 16-20, 22-28, 30, 32, 37, 40, 49.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 109: 1)
      W walce. No. 33-35, 37.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 109: 2)
      WIP, No. 16, 18, 23, 26-27, 29-32, 36-37.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 109: 3--4)
      Walka. Wydanie Srodmiescia. No. 62-80; Walka, No. 53, 55, 75-83.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 109: 5)
      Walka. Warszawski Glos Narodowy. No. 37-42, 44, 46-48, 50-51
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 109: 6)
      Walka o Wolnosc, No. 6.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 109: 7--8)
      Warszawa Walczy, No. 3, 5, 15, 17-20, 22, 24-27, 29-31, 33-35, 37-50, 51-55.
    - Polish Underground Press during World War II, 1944 (Box-folder 109: 9)
      Warszawianka.Wydawnictwo Warszawskiego O.K.R.P.P.S. No. 2, 10, 22.